Stone walls remember what the living forget
돌벽은 산 자들이 잊은 것을 기억한다
Candles flicker where the shadows have wept
그림자가 울었던 곳에 촛불이 흔들린다
I walk these halls in a loop with no end
나는 끝없이 맴도는 이 복도를 걷는다
A ghost dressed in light that the dark cannot bend
어둠조차 꺾지 못하는 빛을 입은 유령
Stained glass colors bleed across the floor
스테인드글라스 빛깔이 바닥 위로 번진다
Every footstep echoes back to the door
발걸음마다 문까지 메아리쳐 돌아온다
I keep on searching for a way to be free
나는 자유로워질 길을 계속 찾는다
But the cathedral holds what's left of me
하지만 대성당은 내 남은 조각을 붙잡고 있다
I haunt the silence between the bells
나는 종소리 사이의 침묵을 맴돈다
A voice that rises where no one dwells
아무도 살지 않는 곳에서 솟아나는 목소리
Through organ pipes and fractured light
오르간 파이프와 조각난 빛 사이로
I am the ghost of a cathedral night
나는 대성당의 밤의 유령
The altar glows with a synthetic flame
제단은 인공적인 불꽃으로 빛난다
Neon crosses spell a forgotten name
네온 십자가는 잊힌 이름을 그려낸다
Time is frozen in a digital haze
시간은 디지털 안개 속에 얼어붙었다
I've been wandering for a thousand days
나는 천 일 동안 헤매고 있었다
I haunt the silence between the bells
나는 종소리 사이의 침묵을 맴돈다
A voice that rises where no one dwells
아무도 살지 않는 곳에서 솟아나는 목소리
Through organ pipes and fractured light
오르간 파이프와 조각난 빛 사이로
I am the ghost of a cathedral night
나는 대성당의 밤의 유령
Let the reverb carry me away
잔향이 나를 싣고 가도록 해줘
Let the bassline guide me through the grey
베이스라인이 잿빛 속 나를 이끌어주게 해줘
I was never meant to disappear
나는 사라질 운명이 아니었다
I was meant to echo here
나는 여기서 메아리칠 운명이었다
I haunt the silence between the bells
나는 종소리 사이의 침묵을 맴돈다
A voice that rises where no one dwells
아무도 살지 않는 곳에서 솟아나는 목소리
Through organ pipes and fractured light
오르간 파이프와 조각난 빛 사이로
I am the ghost of a cathedral night
나는 대성당의 밤의 유령